Guide to the Horizons Theater Company records, 1972-2015 MS2371
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Promotional materials, 1972-2015; 1980-2007; MS2371 Series 4; 8 Linear Feet
  - Press Folders for Take That Ovaries, 2002-2003; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - 2002-2002 Season Info. Sheets, 2002-2003; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Losing Lawrence, 2002-2003; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Ovaries-Press [That Takes Ovaries], 2003; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy Center Millennium Stage, 2003, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - That Takes Ovaries, 2003, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - The South African Project, 2003, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - 2003-2004 Season, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Performances of The South Africa Project, 2003-2005; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Reviews for Count Basil, 2004 June; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Going Solo-Press [Pumping Josey Press], 2004; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Going Solo, 2004; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Press for Pumping Josey: Life and Death in Suburbia, 2004; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - South Africa 2004 [The South African Project Benefit Performance, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Unspoken Prayers, 2004; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Unspoken Prayers Press/Reviews, 2004, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - The Body Project, 2005; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - South Africa [Promo and advertising materials for The South Africa Project], 2005-2006; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - The Body Project Fundraising Event for ANAD, 2006; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Still Going Solo, 2006; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - The Mother/Daughter Project, 2006, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Press, Still Going Solo, 2006, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Horizons Press, 2006-2007, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - SEVEN/DC Seven, 2015, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous promotional material, 1988, 1993, 1999, 2000, 2003-2004, 2006; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Horizons programs, 1998, 2000, 2003, 2005; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Deep Thoughts and Dark Chocolate, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Horizon's PSA Copy, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Jamal's Box, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Peace and Quiet, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Undated Promotional materials, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Photos, unidentified, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Non-Horizons Theatre Productions, 1996, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - CD: The Program, WETA, 2003 June 22; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - CD: Unspoken Prayers, Press Photos, Spring 2004, MS2371 Series 4 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tapes: Interview with Dorothy Parker, WETA, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Keely and Du, undated; MS2371 Series 4 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Financial materials, 1980-2011; 1980-1989; MS2371 Series 5; 2.5 Linear Feet
  The materials of this series include ledgers, budgets, annual financial reports, and donation records. The materials date from 1980-2011.
  The materials found in Boxes 50 and 51 are restricted because they may contain personal or financial information. Please contact Special Collection staff for more information.
  - Fertility Rite - Bills and Box Office, 1980; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Bills Fall 1980 and 90' Festival - B.O., Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - PF1 Budgets, 1980-1983; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Close Calls/Far Cries Business, 1981; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Accountant: C McDermott Correspondence, etc Audit, 1981-1984; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Financial Documents - Accounting, 1981-1982; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Contributions (Photocopies of Checks) Donor Cards, 1982; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Bank Statements, 1982; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Loan Agreement with Leslie, 1982; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Books, 1982-1983; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports, 1982-1983; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Bank Statements: 1982 Checks, Deposit Slips, 1982-1983; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Close Ties Spring 83 Marking Time Fall 82, 1982-1983; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Ticketplace, 1982-1984; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Close Ties: Financial, 1983; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Women's Work - Income Report, 1983; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Box Office: Women's Work, 1983; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Financial Documents - Receipts, 1983-1984; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - 1984 Bills and Receipts, 1983-1984; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Liability Insurance/Workman's Comp Huntington T. Block, 1983-1988; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Financial Management Notes from Daphne's term as manager, 1984; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Top Girls Box Office Reports, 1984; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Sheets Talking With, 1984; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Charges, 1984-1985; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Financial Documents - Payroll Budgets, 1984-1993; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Salaries-Orgasmo Adulto, 1985; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Cash Receipts, 1985-1986; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Horizons - Chart of Accounts and ID Numbers, 1985-1986; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Check Registers, 1985-1986; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Bank Statement Women's National Bank, 1985-1986; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Financial Materials - Horizons Fundraising, 1986; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Income/Expense Ledger, 1986-1987; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements, 1986-1987; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - A... My Name is Alice Expense Reports, 1987; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Invoice - George Thorn, 1987; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Alice Income, 1987; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Marathon Post Ad and Budget, 1987; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Check Logs, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Financial Documents - Payroll, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - DCCAH, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Budget, 1987-1988; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Financial Stuff, 1987-1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Horizons - Financial/Actual Budget Comparison, 1988; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1988; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Pump Boys and Dinettes, 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Liz Ogden/Horizons Theatre, 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - 1st American Bank, 1988-1989; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Huntington T. Block Ins., 1988-1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1989; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - The Stick Wife P.S.A. Press Release Budget, 1989; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Philip Graham Fund, 1989; Series 5 (Box 37, Carton 10)
  - Cultural Alliance, 1989; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Accounts Paid (Misc), 1989-1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Subs, 1989-1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Capital Campaign Expenses, 1989-1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - High Octane Productions, 1989-1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Members List, 1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Dramatists Play Service, 1990; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - DCCAAH GIA, 1991-1994; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Financial Documents - Budgets, 1991-1995; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - The Molly - Leslie Shaw, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Arlington County Foundation - Resume 1999 - $2,000 Living History, Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Contributions to us, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Contributions we make (tickets) and stages, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Yard Sale, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Special Events Costs, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Tomorrowland, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Alice Wills, Paid, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Horizons 1999-2000 ML Add., Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Budget/Brava, Undated; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - 1999 Form 990/Taxes, 1999-2002; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - 1099s ('00-'02), 2000-2002, undated; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - 2004 1099's, MS2371 Series 5 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - 2005 1099s, MS2371 Series 5 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - 2006 1099s, 2006-2007; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - 2007 1099s', 2007-2008; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Taxes 2007 [1/15], MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Taxes 2006 [2/15], MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Taxes 2005 [3/15], MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous tax forms [4/15], 2005; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Taxes 2004 [5/15], MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Taxes 2003 [6/15], MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Taxes 2002 [7/15], MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Taxes 2001 [8/15], MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous tax forms [9/15], 1995, 1997-2000; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Tax 98,99,00 [10/15], 1998-2000; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Taxes 1994-1993 [11/15], 1993-1994; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous tax forms [12/15], 1991-1993, 1995; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - IRS Notices [13/15], 1999, 2004, 2007-2008; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous tax forms [14/15], 1987-1994, 2011, undated; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - IRS Tax Exempt Letter [15/15], circa 1980s; MS2371 Series 5 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Productions and stage notes, 1978-2006; MS2371 Series 6; 2 Linear Feet
  The materials of this series include production notes, compiled research for scripts or productions, stage diagrams, illustrations, and annotated scripts. The materials date from 1978-2006.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Notes-Pro Femina, 1978-1981; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Plays-Motherhouses Notes, 1979; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Ticketplace: Marking Time Notes, other info (Box Office), 1982; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Timetable-Cast, 1983; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Close Ties-Stage Notes, 1983; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Women's Work-Minutes/Flyers, 1983; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Plays-Women's Work, 1983-1985; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Last Days at the Dixie Girl Cafe-Sketch, 1985; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Mrs. California Stage Notes, 1986-1987; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Absent Minded Sweethearts-Stage Notes, 1987; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - AMS Original Concept Draft, 1987; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Still Life Notes, 1987; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Background Slides-Absent Minded Sweethearts and Still Life, 1987; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Still Life-Stage Notes, 1987; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Ms. Montage, 1989; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Reckless-Stage Notes, 1990; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Rhythms-Stage Notes, 1994; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Kindertransport-Stage Notes, 1995; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - That Takes Ovaries! Notes, 2003; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Unknown-Sketches and Notes, Undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Plays-Unknown Musical Score, Undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Recording-Motherhouses, 1979; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Recording-Dear Esther, 1998; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Sylvia's Real Good Advice, 1991 August; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Sunday Blues and Acts of Devotion, circa 1995; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Notes and Research for In Good Company, circa 1998; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Dear Esther, 1997; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Unspoken Prayers -Post-Show Discussion, 2004; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Fatland [Bulletins from Fatland Script with notes and other related materials, circa 1995, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Birth, 2005-2006; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Communion, and Deep Thoughts and Dark Chocolate from Still Going Solo, 2006, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Unspoken Prayers, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - I Want to Tell You, with song lyrics and notes, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Personal notes about the female body/Letters to My Body Project, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - The Body Project Notes, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - The Body Project notes and annotated script, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Costume change notes, unidentified show, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified production, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Unidentified production, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Horizons Theatre production photographs, 1988, 1993-1995, 1997; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - DVD: Count Basil at Fordham University, 2003 August 3; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Songs used for a production, undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous notes [1/2], undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous notes [2/2], undated; MS2371 Series 6 (Box 61, Folder 3)